Their streets. Their rules.
Brick Mansions is a action, crime, drama film directed by Camille Delamarre.
In a dystopian Detroit, grand houses that once housed the wealthy
are now homes of the city's most-dangerous criminals.
Surrounding the area is a giant wall to keep the rest of Detroit safe.
For undercover cop Damien Collier, every day is a battle against corruption as
he struggles to bring his father's killer, Tremaine, to justice.
Meanwhile, Damien and an ex-con named Lino work together to
save the city from a plot to destroy it.
Damien Collier, played by Paul Walker.
Lino, played by David Belle.
Tremaine, played by RZA.
Yeti, played by Robert Maillet.
George the Greek, played by Carlo Rota.
Mayor's Assistant, played by Kalinka Pétrie.
Brick Mansions is a 2014 action film starring Paul Walker, David
Belle, RZA, Goûchy Boy, Catalina Denis and Carlo Rota.
The film was directed by Camille Delamarre and written by Luc
Besson, Robert Mark Kamen and Bibi Naceri.
A co-production between France, Canada and the United States, it is a remake of
the 2004 French film District 13, in which Belle had also starred.
This movie was released on April 25, 2014, five months after Walker's
death on November 30, 2013, and is dedicated to him.
This was Walker's last fully completed film before his death and his
penultimate film, followed by his final film appearance in Furious 7.
The film explores themes of martial arts, atomic
bomb, gangster, dystopia, ghetto.
The tone is emotional.